Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music collection
  - 12 inch vinyl
    - Numbered by Bambaataa
      - 750 - Steam., 1970; SR-8455-8456; Steam (Musical group) (Box 122)
        Title on container: Na na hey hey kiss him good-bye and Come on back and love me.
      - 751 - Multiplication rock: original soundtrack from the ABC-TV series, 1973; SR-8457; Dorough, Bob. (Box 122)
      - 752 - Malombo., 1976; SR-8458 (Box 122)
      - 752 - Malombo., 1976; SR-8459 (Box 122)
      - 753 - Get up and dance, 1977; SR-8460; Memphis Horns. (Box 122)
      - 754 - Best of the early years. Volume one, 1974; SR-9213; Funkadelic (Musical group) (Box 122)
      - 755 - Westbound LP sampler., 1973-1977; SR-8461 (Box 122)
        "Not for sale."
        Westbound Records Inc.
      - 756 - Thirsty or not-- choose your flavor., 1977; SR-8462-8463; Coalkitchen (Musical group) (Box 122)
      - 756 - Thirsty or not-- choose your flavor., Coalkitchen (Musical group) (Box 122)
      - 757 - Rated extraordinaire., 1977; SR-8464; Taylor, Johnnie. (Box 122)
      - 758 - Reaching for the world, 1976; SR-8465; Melvin, Harold. (Box 122)
        Millennium
      - 759 - Joy ride, 1976; SR-8466; Dramatics (Musical group) (Box 122)
      - 760 - Going first class, 1976; SR-8467; First Class (Musical group) (Box 122)
        Promotional copy, Not for sale._x000D_ Matrix / Runout (A-side label): (AP-4032-GM); Matrix / Runout (B-side label): (AP-4033-GM)
        Planet Rock Music
      - 761 - Exodus, 1977; SR-9214; Marley, Bob. (Box 122)
      - 761 - Exodus, 1977; SR-9215; Marley, Bob. (Box 122)
        Matrix nos.: ILPS 9498 A-4; ILPS 9498 B-6._x000D_
        Pitman, New Jersey
      - 762 - Ice on fire, 1977; SR-9216; Mighty Diamonds (Musical group) (Box 122)
        Virgin Records
      - 763 - Full bloom., 1978; SR-8468 (Box 122)
      - 764 - Floaters., 1977; SR-8469; Floaters (Musical group) (Box 122)
      - 765 - Sweet passion, 1977; SR-8470; Franklin, Aretha. (Box 122)
      - 766 - When was the last time, 1976; sr-8472; Little Beaver (Vocalist) (Box 122)
        Cat Records
      - 767 - Never say you can't survive., 1977; SR-9217; Mayfield, Curtis. (Box 122)
      - 768 - Fly like an eagle, 1976; SR-8473-8474; Miller, Steve, 1943 October 5- (Box 122)
      - 769 - He's all I've got, 1976; SR-8475; White, Barry, 1944-2003. (Box 122)
        Unlimited Gold Records
      - 770 - This is Niecy, 1976; SR-9218; Williams, Deniece. (Box 122)
      - 771 - Wood, Brass & Steel., 1976; SR-8476; Wood, Brass & Steel (Musical group) (Box 122)
        Turbo
      - 772 - Festival, 1976; SR-8477; Santana (Musical group) (Box 122)
        On container: PC 34423._x000D_
      - 773 - One to one, 1977; SR-9219; Syreeta. (Box 122)
      - 774 - Angel, 1977; SR-9220; Ohio Players (Musical group), (Box 122)
      - 775 - Eugene Record., 1977; SR-8478; Record, Eugene. (Box 122)
      - 776 - Equal rights, 1977; SR-9221; Tosh, Peter. (Box 122)
      - 777 - Good news, 1977; SR-8481 (Box 122)
      - 778 - Jeanne, 1976; SR-8482; Napoli, Jeanne. (Box 122)
        "D.J. copy - not for sale."
      - 778 - Jeanne, 1976; SR-8483; Napoli, Jeanne. (Box 123)
      - 779 - Mandre¿¿., 1977; SR-8484; Mandre¿¿. (Box 123)
      - 779 - Mandre¿¿., 1977; SR-8485; Mandre¿¿. (Box 123)
      - 780 - Golden girls, 1977; SR-9222; Silver Convention (Musical group) (Box 123)
      - 780 - Slave., 1977; SR-8486-8487; Slave (Musical group) (Box 123)
      - 781 - Last night on earth., 1977; SR-8488; Rhythm Heritage (Musical group) (Box 123)
      - 781 - New York Community Choir., 1977; SR-8489; New York Community Choir. (Box 123)
      - 782 - Smooth as silk, 1977; SR-8491; Silk (Soul group) (Box 123)
        Prelude Records
      - 782 - Yesterday, today & tomorrow, 1977; SR-8490; Spinners (Musical group: U.S.) (Box 123)
      - 783 - Karen Pree., 1977; SR-8492; Pree, Karen. (Box 123)
      - 784 - Oops! here I go again, 1977; SR-9653; Wright, Edna. (Box 140)
      - 784 - Sweet beginnings, 1977; SR-8493; Shaw, Marlena. (Box 123)
      - 785 - Stay in love, 1977; SR-9223; Riperton, Minnie. (Box 123)
      - 785 - All my life., 1976; SR-8494; Prysock, Arthur. (Box 123)
        Old Town
      - 786 - Let 'em in, 1976; SR-8496; Paul, Billy. (Box 123)
      - 786 - Hot Ice no. 1, 1976; SR-8495; Hot Ice (Disco group) (Box 123)
        Rage Records
        Carson, California
      - 787 - Big daddy's place, 1977; SR-8497; Henderson, Wayne, 1939-2014. (Box 123)
      - 787 - Havin' a house party, 1977; SR-8498; Hutch, Willie. (Box 123)
      - 788 - Cardiac arrest, 1977; SR-8329; Cameo (Musical group) (Box 123)
        Chocolate City: Distributed by Casablanca Records
      - 789 - Here & now, 1977; SR-8500; Cherry, Don. (Box 123)
      - 789 - Universal language, 1977; SR-8499; Booker T. & the MG's (Musical group) (Box 123)
      - 790 - Give & take, 1977; SR-8502; Dynamic Superiors (Musical group) (Box 123)
      - 790 - Izitso, 1977; SR-8501; Stevens, Californiat, 1948- (Box 123)
      - 791 - In good taste, 1976; SR-8505; Flavor (Soul group) (Box 123)
        Ju-Par Records
      - 791 - Waters., 1977; SR-8503; Waters (Musical group) (Box 123)
      - Party, party, 1977; SR-8504; Waters (Musical group) (Box 123)
        Not numbered, housed with SR-8503. This is a promotional item._x000D_ Disco mix._x000D__x000D_ From the Warner Bros album, BS 3062 Waters.
      - 792 - John Payne, 1977; SR-8506; Levin, Louis. (Box 123)
      - 792 - We belong together, 1977; SR-8507; Blair, John (Vocalist) (Box 123)
        CTI Records
      - 793 - Universal child, 1977; SR-8508; Steinberg, Dianne. (Box 123)
        This is a Demontration Copy.
      - 794 - Music inspired by Star wars and other galactic funk, 1977; SR-8509; Williams, John, 1932- (Box 123)
      - 794 - Whitney Family airways, 1977; SR-8510; Whitney Family (Musical group) (Box 123)
      - 795 - Super star; Everybody's fool, 1977; SR-8512-8513 (Box 123)
      - 795 - Sun-power, 1977; SR-8511; Sun (Musical group: Dayton, Ohio) (Box 123)
        Pressed on clear, orange vinyl._x000D_
      - 796 - In flight, 1977; SR-8514; Benson, George, 1943- (Box 123)
      - 797 - Shout it out, 1977; SR-8516; Rushen, Patrice. (Box 123)
      - 797 - Harmony, 1977; SR-8515; Person, Houston. (Box 123)
      - 799 - I'm in you., 1977; SR-8518; Frampton, Peter. (Box 123)
      - 799 - Anacostia., 1977; SR-8517 (Box 123)
      - 800 - Man with the sad face., 1976; SR-8519; Turrentine, Stanley. (Box 123)
      - 801 - Metamorphosis, 1976; SR-8520; Marcus, Wade. (Box 123)
      - 804 - Right on time., 1977; SR-8521 (Box 123)
      - 807 - Bridgetown Barbados, 1970-1979; SR-8522; Sandpebbles of Barbados (Musical group) (Box 123)
        Matrix / Runout (side 1): PG-1012-S1; Matrix / Runout (side 2): PG-1012-S2._x000D_
      - 808 - Professionals on tour., 1971; SR-9224; Professionals (Musical group: Jesu¿¿s Acosta) (Box 124)
        CES
        Belize City, B.H.
      - 809 - Art of mas, 1977; SR-8523; Lee, Byron. (Box 124)
        Title from disc label.
        Dynamic Sounds
      - 810 - Sokah rocky sokah, 1977; SR-8524; Matt, Ellie. (Box 124)
      - 813 - Black gold, 1970; SR-8525; Simone, Nina, 1933-2003. (Box 124)
      - 814 - Too hot to handle, 1976; SR-8526; Temperton, Rod. (Box 124)
      - 815 - Sylvester., 1977; SR-8527 (Box 124)
      - 817 - Osibirock, 1974; SR-9225; Osibisa (Musical group) (Box 124)
      - 818 - Cinderella (Queen of the dance); Hymn for Africa, 1977; SR-8528; Daniel Jackson Explosion (Musical group) (Box 124)
        Pressed in red opaque vinyl.
        Blu Records
        Italy
      - 819 - Afrovision, 1977; SR-8529; Dibango, Manu, 1933- (Box 124)
        Telson
      - 820 - What's on your mind, 1977; SR-9226; Hodges, James & Smith (Musical group) (Box 124)
        London Disco
      - 821 - Kraftwerk., 1972; SR-8530-8531; Kraftwerk (Musical group) (Box 124)
        England?
      - 822 - Cream city, 1977; SR-8602; Aalon (Musical group) (Box 125)
        "Promotion copy, Not for Sale."_x000D_
      - 823 - Erotic soul; I'm hooked on you, 1976; SR-8532-8533; Blackwell, Charles, (Box 124)
      - 824 - Bite your granny; Feelin' strong, 1977; SR-8534; Morning, Noon & Night (Musical group) (Box 124)
        "DJ use only, Not for Sale"--Disc label._x000D_ "From the Roadshow LP "Morning, Noon & Night" RS-LA726-G
        Rodadshow: Distributed by United Artists
      - 826 - Theme from Disco 77, 1976-1977; SR-8535-8536; Sassy (Musical group) (Box 124)
      - 827 - Vibrations, 1976; SR-8537; Ayers, Roy. (Box 124)
      - 829 - That's all., 1977; SR-8538 (Box 124)
      - 830 - Whole nother thang, 1976; SR-8539-8540; Haskins, Fuzzy, 1941- (Box 124)
      - 830 - Whole nother thang, Haskins, Fuzzy, 1941- (Box 124)
      - 831 - Real ting!, 1976; SR-9227; Minnis, Eddie. (Box 124)
        Posh Boy
      - 832 - Variations, 1977; SR-8541; Variations (Musical group) (Box 124)
        Amour Records
        Oakland, California
      - 833 - Soseme Makonde; Manzara, 1977; SR-9228; Makonde (Musical group) (Box 124)
        Blue vinyl._x000D_ Special disco mix
        EMI
        Netherlands
      - 834 - Watch out!, 1977; SR-8542; Trax (Musical group) (Box 124)
      - 835 - Ram Jam., 1977; SR-8543 (Box 124)
      - 836 - Cosmic wind, 1977; SR-8544-8545; Theodore, Mike. (Box 124)
      - 837 - Behold the mighty army, 1977; SR-8547; New Birth (Musical group) (Box 124)
      - 837 - Behold the mighty army, 1977; SR-8546; New Birth (Musical group) (Box 124)
      - 838 - Action, Blackbyrds (Box 124)
      - 839 - Kings of clubs., 1977; SR-8549 (Box 124)
      - 839 - Kings of clubs., 1977; SR-8548 (Box 124)
      - 840 - Cocomotion, 1977; SR-8550 (Box 124)
      - 841 - High energy, 1975; SR-8551; Sly & the Family Stone (Musical group) (Box 124)
      - 842 - Doin' it to the bone, 1977; SR-8552; Muscle Shoals Horns. (Box 124)
        Ariola America
      - 843 - Turns you on, 1976; SR-8553; Fancy (Musical group) (Box 124)
      - 844 - Macumba, 1977; SR-8554; Marboo (Musician) (Box 124)
        Columbia: Manufactured by CBS Records Canada
        Don Mills, Ontario
      - 845 - 5 Stairsteps., 1970; SR-8555; Stairsteps (Musical group) (Box 124)
      - 846 - Feel the fire., 1977; SR-8556 (Box 124)
      - 847 - Turn it out., 1977; SR-8557 (Box 124)
      - 848 - Erotic soul, 1977; SR-8532-8533; Blackwell, Charles, (Box 124)
        "London Promotional copy Not For Sale"
      - 849 - Maze, 1977; SR-8558-8559; Beverly, Frankie. (Box 124)
      - 850 - Mastermind, Mastermind (Box 124)
      - 851 - Welcome to the canteen, 1971; SR-8560 (Box 124)
      - 852 - We are one, 1977; SR-8562; Mandrill (Musical group) (Box 125)
      - 852 - We are one, 1977; SR-8561; Mandrill (Musical group) (Box 124)
      - 855 - Cuchi-cuchi, 1977; SR-8563; Charo. (Box 125)
      - 856 - Love shook, 1977; SR-8564; Brooks, Pattie. (Box 125)
      - 857 - Ashantis., 1977; SR-6877; Ashantis (Musical group) (Box 5)
        Sterling
      - 858 - Funk reaction, 1977; SR-8565 (Box 125)
        Les Disques Direction Records
      - 859 - Off the wall, 1977; SR-8566; Fat Larry's Band. (Box 125)
      - 860 - Letter from Miami, 1977; SR-9229; Hylton, Sheila. (Box 125)
        Harmless Recordings
      - 861 - Peace and love, 1975; SR-9230; Thompson, Linval. (Box 125)
        Full Time
      - 862 - Certified live., 1976; SR-8567-8568 (Box 125)
      - 864 - Gotta groove, 1969; SR-8569; Bar-Kays (Musical group) (Box 125)
      - 864 - Gotta groove., 1979; SR-8570 (Box 125)
      - 865 - Cutting the chord, 1977; SR-8571; Mother Freedom Band. (Box 125)
        "Promotion copy, Not for Sale."
        All Platinum
      - 866 - Menagerie, 1977; SR-8572; Withers, Bill, 1938- (Box 125)
      - 867 - Hot lunch, 1977; SR-8573; Fisher, Eddie, 1943-2007. (Box 125)
        Platinum Record Co.
      - 868 - Cherish, 1977; SR-8574; Hudson, Al. (Box 125)
      - 869 - Disco delivery, 1977; SR-8575; D. D. Sound (Musical Group) (Box 125)
        Baby
      - 870 - Greatest, 1977; SR-8576; Masser, Michael, 1941- (Box 125)
        Based on The Greatest; my own story, by Muhammad Ali, Herbert Muhammad and Richard Durham._x000D_
      - 871 - Protest., 1977; SR-9231; Wailer, Bunny. (Box 125)
        California
      - 872 - We're all in this together, 1977; SR-8577; Toussaint, Allen R. (Box 125)
      - 873 - Say my friend, 1977; SR-8684; Rance Allen Group. (Box 125)
      - 874 - 'Lectric lady, 1976; SR-8578 (Box 125)
      - 875 - Nice 'n' naasty, 1976; SR-9654 (Box 140)
        Salsoul Record Corporation
      - 876 - Lonnie Youngblood., 1977; SR-8579; Youngblood, Lonnie, 1941- (Box 125)
      - 877 - Moments greatest hits, 1977; SR-8580-8581; Moments (Musical group) (Box 125)
        Stang Records
      - 879 - Two of us, 1977; SR-9400; McCoo, Marilyn. (Box 125)
      - 880 - People get up; I believe in music, 1977; SR-8582; Mass Production (Musical group) (Box 125)
        From Cotillion LP 9918._x000D_ Promotional._x000D_ Matrix / Runout (A-Side Label): ST-DSKO-33758-PR Matrix / Runout (B-Side Label): ST-DSKO-33759-PR.
      - 881 - Love shock., 1977; SR-8583 (Box 125)
      - 884 - Was dog a doughnut?: disco version, 1977; SR-8584; Stevens, Californiat, 1948- (Box 125)
        "Promotional copy--not for sale."_x000D_
      - 885 - Doin' that crazy thing, 1977; SR-8585; Lynne, Jeff. (Box 141)
        United Artists Records/Jet Records
      - 886 - Willie Dynamite soundtrack, Johnson, J.J. (Box 125)
      - 887 - Flying high on your love., 1977; SR-8586 (Box 125)
      - 888 - Ce¿¿ pe¿¿che, 1977; SR-8587; Mini All Stars (Musical group) (Box 125)
        Million Dollar Records: Distributed by ABC Records
      - 889 - Running away, 1977; SR-8588; Ubiquity (Musical group) (Box 125)
        Special disco version from Polydor album PD-1-6108 "Lifeline".
      - 890 - News of the world., 1977; SR-8589-8590; Queen (Musical group) (Box 125)
      - 890 - News of the world., Queen (Musical group) (Box 125)
      - 891 - Kiss me (the way I like it); Kiss me (the way I like it) (pt.2), 1977; SR-8591-8592; McCrae, George. (Box 125)
      - 892 - Man with the band, 1977; SR-9232; Fatback (Musical group) (Box 125)
        Spring Records: Polydor distributor
      - 893 - Moonflower., 1977; SR-8593-8594; Santana (Musical group) (Box 125)
        Columbia: 34914--34916 (on container: C2 34914)_x000D_
      - 894 - On fire; Disco magic, 1977; SR-8595-8596; T-Connection (Musical group) (Box 125)
        Taken from LP "On fire" (Dash 30008), and, "Magic" (Dash 30001).
      - 895 - Ffun; ConFunkShunizeYa, 1977; SR-8597; Con-Funk-Shun (Musical group) (Box 125)
        "Promotional copy, Not for Sale."_x000D_ From Mercury's album "Secrets" SRM-1-1180.
      - 897 - Disco Bill., 1977; SR-8598; Cosby, Bill, 1937- (Box 125)
      - 898 - Brass construction III, 1977; SR-8599; Brass Construction (Musical group) (Box 125)
        Matrix / Runout (Side 1 run-out etching): UALA 775-1 FWapple; Matrix / Runout (Side 2 run-out etching): UALA 775-2 FWapple.
      - 899 - Maximum stimulation, 1977; SR-8600-8601; Jimmy Castor Bunch. (Box 140)
      - 900 - L.A. bound., 1977; SR-8603 (Box 125)
      - 901 - Cerrone 3: supernature., 1977; SR-8604; Cerrone. (Box 126)
      - 902 - New horizons, 1977; SR-8605; Sylvers (Musical group) (Box 126)
      - 903 - Sons of the gods., 1977; SR-8606 (Box 126)
      - 904 - Moon-boots, 1977; SR-8607; Monn, Anthony, (Box 126)
        Salsoul Records: Tom n' Jerry Records
      - 905 - Love for sale., 1977; SR-8608 (Box 126)
      - 906 - Bionic Boogie., 1977; SR-8609; Diamond, Gregg, (Box 126)
      - 907 - Portrait of Melba., 1977; SR-8610 (Box 126)
        Poster inserted in container.
      - 908 - Van McCoy and his magnificent movie machine., 1977; SR-8611 (Box 126)
      - 909 - Commodores live., 1977; SR-8612-8613; Commodores (Musical group) (Box 126)
      - 910 - Mr. Mean, 1977; SR-8614-8615; Ohio Players (Musical group) (Box 126)
      - 911 - All 'n all, 1977; SR-8616; Earth, Wind & Fire (Musical group), (Box 126)
        CBS
      - 911 - All 'n all, 1977; SR-8617; Earth, Wind & Fire (Musical group), (Box 126)
      - 912 - Funkentelechy vs. the placebo syndrome, 1977; SR-9233; Parliament (Musical group), (Box 126)
      - 912 - Funkentelechy vs. the placebo syndrome, 1977; SR-8618; Parliament (Musical group), (Box 126)
      - 913 - Mama let him play., 1977; SR-8619; Doucette (Musical group) (Box 126)
      - 913 - Mama let him play., 1977; SR-8620; Doucette (Musical group) (Box 126)
        Mushroom Records
      - 914 - Riding high., 1977; SR-8621 (Box 126)
        She
      - 915 - Goin' bananas., 1977; SR-8622; Side Effect (Musical group) (Box 126)
      - 916 - Wilbur Bascomb and Future Dreams., 1977; SR-8623-8624 (Box 126)
      - 917 - Two hot for love!, 1977; SR-8625; THP Orchestra. (Box 126)
        Butterfly Records
      - 919 - Trini-vibes, 1977; SR-9234; Kalyan (Musical group) (Box 126)
      - 920 - From South Africa to South Carolina, 1975; SR-8626; Scott-Heron, Gil, 1949-2011. (Box 126)
      - 921 - Rock bottom, 1975; SR-8627-8628; Bottom & Co. (Musical group) (Box 126)
      - 922 - Fela & Afrika 70., 1977; SR-9235; Fela, 1938-1997. (Box 126)
      - 923 - De zess man, 1978; SR-8629; Shadow (Calypso singer) (Box 126)
      - 924 - Funky highlife, 1975; SR-8630; Mann, C. K. (Box 126)
      - 925 - On fire, 1977; SR-8631; T-Connection (Musical group) (Box 126)
      - 925 - On fire, 1977; SR-8632-8633; T-Connection (Musical group) (Box 126)
      - 925 - On fire, T-Connection (Musical group) (Box 126)
      - 925 - On fire, T-Connection (Musical group) (Box 126)
      - 926 - Afrodisiac, 1973; SR-9236; Fela, 1938-1997. (Box 126)
        Regal Zonophone
      - 927 - Just laying it down; You like it, we love it, 1977; SR-8634; Job, Lionel, (Box 126)
        Luke Skywalker
        Liberty City, Florida
      - 928 - Trinidad, 1977; SR-8635; Gibbs, John A. (Box 126)
        "From the album Steel Funk (SSR606)--Jacket.
        Solid Steel Records
      - 929 - I am a photograph, 1977; SR-8636; Lear, Amanda. (Box 126)
        Chrysalis Records
      - 930 - Disco boogie., 1977; SR-8637-8638 (Box 126)
      - 931 - Shout it out, 1977; SR-8639; B.T. Express (Musical group) (Box 126)
        Special disco version of the Columbia single: 3-10649._x000D_ Demonstration, Not for Sale.
      - 932 - Everything scatter; Who no know go know, 1976; SR-9237; Fela, 1938-1997. (Box 126)
      - 932 - Ole'ELO, 1976; SR-8640; Electric Light Orchestra. (Box 126)
      - 933 - Johnny Reason., 1977; SR-8641 (Box 126)
        At-Home
      - 934 - Star discs., 1977; SR-8642-8643 (Box 127)
      - 935 - Dr. Buzzard's Original Savannah Band meets King Penett., 1978; SR-8644-8645; Browder, Stony. (Box 127)
      - 937 - Golden tears, 1978; SR-8646 (Box 127)
      - 938 - Gordon's war, 1973; SR-8647; Elias, Al. (Box 127)
        Manufacturer's number on container: BDS-5137ST.
      - 939 - Mellow madness, 1975; SR-8648; Jones, Quincy, 1933- (Box 127)
        Poster (38 x 56 cm. fold. to 28 x 28 cm.) inserted.
      - 941 - Let's all chant; Love express, 1977; SR-8649; Michael Zager Band. (Box 127)
        Private Stock Records
      - 942 - Weekend in L.A., 1978; SR-8652-8653 (Box 127)
        Jazz._x000D_ Record discs are ordered for automatic sequencing. Duplicate 2-album release except slightly different publisher's no.: 2WB 3139 with C below number; also matrix: 2WB 3139 1A-2G
      - 942 - Weekend in L.A., 1978; SR-8650-8651 (Box 127)
      - 943 - Force, 1977; SR-8654 (Box 127)
        De-Lite Recorded Sound Corp.
      - 944 - Kilowatt, 1978; SR-8655; Kay-Gees (Musical group) (Box 127)
      - 944 - Kilowatt, 1978; SR-8656; Kay-Gees (Musical group) (Box 127)
      - 945 - On my way, 1978; SR-8657; Bohannon, Hamilton. (Box 127)
        Mercury: Phonogram
      - 946 - Melodies: (vocal); Gotta get a high, 1977; SR-8658 (Box 127)
      - 947 - Let me party with you, 1977; SR-8659; Sigler, Bunny. (Box 127)
        Gibbous; Distributed by Release Records
      - 948 - Three piece suit, 1977; SR-9238; Trinity (Musician) (Box 127)
        Released without publisher no.
        Joe Gibbs Music Corp.
        Opa-Locka, Florida
      - 949 - Johnnymelfi's sun...sun...sun album, 1977; SR-8660; Melfi, Johnny. (Box 127)
      - 950 - Sylvers III., 1974; sr-8661-8662; Sylvers (Musical group) (Box 127)
      - 952 - Disco fantasy, 1977; SR-9664; Escovedo, Coke. (Box 141)
      - 953 - Raydio., 1978; SR-8663; Raydio (Musical group) (Box 127)
      - 954 - N.Y.C. blackout, 1978; SR-8664; Sparrow (Calypso singer) (Box 127)
      - 955 - Her majesty, 1978; SR-8665; Calypso Rose. (Box 127)
        C.L.O. Records; Charlie's Records
        Trinidad
      - 956 - Melodies of the 21st century, 1978; SR-8666; Kitchener, Lord. (Box 127)
      - 957 - Prana people., 1977; SR-8667; Prana People (Musical group) (Box 127)
      - 958 - Path, 1978; SR-8668-8669; MacDonald, Ralph. (Box 127)
      - 959 - Piece of the action: original sound track music, 1977; SR-9239-9240; Mayfield, Curtis. (Box 127)
      - 960 - House of the rising sun, 1978; SR-8670; Santa Esmeralda (Musical group) (Box 127)
      - 961 - Kaiso., 1973; SR-8671 (Box 127)
        Ra Records
      - 963 - Funk in a Mason jar, 1977; SR-8672; Mason, Harvey, 1947- (Box 127)
      - 964 - Mr. Rhythm, 1976; SR-8673; King, Sporty. (Box 127)
        Konduko
      - 965 - Bootsy? Player of the year, 1978; SR-9241; Bootsy's Rubber Band. (Box 127)
      - 967 - Bionic Boogie., 1977; SR-8674; Diamond, Gregg. (Box 127)
        White label; promotional copy._x000D_ For radio programming only._x000D_ Selections from the Polydor album PD-1-6123, Bionic Boogie.
      - 968 - Saturday night fever: original movie soundtrack., 1977; SR-8675-8676 (Box 127)
      - 969 - Last days and time, 1972; SR-8677; Earth, Wind & Fire (Musical group) (Box 127)
      - 970 - Dogs of War, 1977; SR-6762; Dogs of War (Musical group) (Box 2)
        General Recording Corp.
      - 971 - Romeo & Juliet, 1978; SR-8678; Costandinos, Alec R. (Box 127)
        Promotional copy; not for sale._x000D_
      - 972 - Once upon a time--, 1977; SR-9242-9243; Summer, Donna. (Box 127)
      - 973 - Starbooty, 1978; SR-8679; Ubiquity (Musical group) (Box 127)
      - 974 - Formerly of the Harlettes., 1978; SR-8680 (Box 127)
      - 975 - Burning Spear, live., 1977; SR-9244 (Box 128)
      - 977 - 96¿¿ in the shade, 1977; SR-9245; Third World (Musical group) (Box 128)
      - 979 - Up the yellow brick road, 1978; SR-8681; Salsoul Orchestra. (Box 128)
      - 980 - USA-European Connection., 1978; SR-8683 (Box 128)
        Florida
      - 980 - USA-European Connection., 1978; SR-8682 (Box 128)
      - 981 - Pleasure principle, 1978; SR-9640; Parlet (Musical group) (Box 128)
      - 982 - Je taime, 1979; SR-8685; St. Tropez (Musical group) (Box 128)
        Pressed on clear pink vinyl, in gatefold sleeve._x000D_
      - 983 - Kebekelektrik., 1977; SR-8686 (Box 128)
        Diable Noir Records: Virgin Records
      - 983 - Kebekelektrik., 1977; SR-8687 (Box 128)
        Direction
        St. Laurent, Quebec
      - 984 - Fast, 1977; SR-8688; Randy Pie (Musical group) (Box 128)
      - 985 - Hardness of the world., 1977; SR-8689 (Box 128)
      - 986 - Let's do it., 1978; SR-8690; Ayers, Roy. (Box 128)
      - 988 - Frontiers., 1978; SR-8691 (Box 128)
      - 990 - Macho man, 1978; SR-8692; Village People, (Box 128)
      - 991 - B & G rhythm., 1978; SR-8693; B & G Rhythm (Musical group) (Box 128)
        "For radio programming only" "Not for Sale Promotional copy" From Polydor album PD-1-6132._x000D_
      - 992 - Get off, 1978; SR-8694; Foxy (Musical group) (Box 128)
        Dash
      - 994 - Eyesight; Spank, 1978; SR-8695; Brown, James, 1933-2006. (Box 128)